http://www.marist.edu/privacy-policy

Disclaimers/Privacy Policy/
This is the Privacy Policy of the website of www.marist.edu. This policy does not cover privacy for the use of College owned equipment or other information resources. Use of College equipment and other information resources are covered in the Information Security Policy, found at http://security.marist.edu
Our postal address is:
Marist College
3399 North Road
Poughkeepsie, NY 12601
We can be reached via email at web.services@marist.edu or by telephone at 845-575-3252.
Privacy Policy
Marist College is committed to respecting your privacy as a customer. Our privacy policy is clear: We collect no information about you, other than information automatically collected and stored, when you visit our Web site unless you choose to provide that information to us. We may combine the information we collect from you with information obtained from other sources to help us improve its overall accuracy and completeness, and to help us better tailor our interactions with you. In addition, we may also collect information relating to your use of our Web site through the use of various technologies, including cookies.
Information Automatically Collected
When you browse through any Web site, certain information about you can be collected. We automatically collect and temporarily store the following information about your visit:
the date and time of your visit;
IP address;
browser type, operating system and language;
the pages you visited; and
the address of the Web site from which you came.
We use this information for statistical purposes and to help us make our site more useful to visitors. Unless it is specifically stated otherwise, no additional information is collected about you.
Portions of the Marist Web site use Google Analytics, which uses cookies to collect anonymous traffic data. By using this web site, you consent to the processing of data about you by Google in the manner and for the purposes set out above. You may review Google's full privacy policy at: http://www.google.com/privacypolicy.html.
Personally Provided Information
Marist College does not require you provide to personal information to visit our Web site; however, you may choose to provide us with personal information through an email message, form, survey, etc. This information is used only to fulfill the stated purpose of your communication and/or participation.
Cookies, Web Beacons and Other Technologies
As mentioned above, we collect information from your visits to our Web sites to help us gather statistics about our Web sites usage and effectiveness, personalize your experience on our sites, and tailor our interactions with you.
We do so through the use of various technologies, including one called "cookies". A cookie is a piece of data that a Web site can send to your browser, which may then be stored on your computer as a tag that identifies your computer. While cookies are often only used to measure Web site usage and effectiveness and to allow for ease of navigation or use and as such, are not associated with any personal information, they are also used at times to personalize a known visitor’s experience to a Web site by being associated with profile information or user preferences. You can set your browser in most instances to notify you before you receive a cookie, giving you the chance to decide whether to accept it or not. You can also generally set your browser to turn off cookies. Since cookies allow you to take advantage of some of our Web sites’ features, we recommend that you leave them turned on.
Some Web sites also use Web beacon or other technologies to better tailor those sites to provide better customer service. These technologies may be in use on a number of pages across Web sites. When a visitor accesses these pages, a non identifiable notice of that visit is generated which may be processed by us or by our suppliers. These Web beacons usually work in conjunction with cookies. If you don't want your cookie information to be associated with your visits to these pages, you can set your browser to turn off cookies. If you turn off cookies, Web beacon and other technologies will still detect visits to these pages; however, they will not be associated with information otherwise stored in cookies.
We may also include Web beacons in marketing e-mail messages or our newsletters in order to determine whether messages have been opened and links contained within clicked on.
Some of our business partners set Web beacons and cookies on our site. In addition third-party social media buttons may log certain information such as your IP address, browser type and language, access time, and referring Web site addresses, and, if you are logged in to those social media sites, they may also link such collected information with your profile information on that site. We do not control these third party tracking technologies.
Disclosure
Marist College does not give, sell or transfer any personal information about our online visitors to third parties except as required by law.
Endorsement Disclaimer
Our Web site has links to many other non-profit, educational, and governmental institutions, and in a few cases, private organizations. You are subject to that site's Privacy Policy when you leave this site. Reference in this Web site to any specific service, company, or organization does not constitute its endorsement or recommendation by Marist College. Marist College is not responsible for the contents of any "off-site" Web page referenced from this server.
Changes to the policy
If our information practices change at some time in the future, we will post the policy changes to our website to notify you of these changes.
[Updated 5/2012]
